A racing second hand, a glittering shooting star!
عقرب دقائق مسرِع، مُذنّب لامع
Conan's logic is good medicine for hearts dried by modern society!
استنتاجات كونان دواء ممتاز للقلوب !التي جفّفها المجتمع الحديث
Today's case is a bank robbery! But something's a little off!
!قضيّة اليوم عن سرقة مصرف !لكن هنالك أمر غريب
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Wow! A turkey!
!مٌذهل! 3 إسقاطات متتالية
That was fun!
!كان ذلك مُسلياً
Bowling alleys are nice and empty on weekdays!
من الرائع الذهاب لقاعات البولينغ عندما تكون فارغةً أيام الأسبوع
Definitely!
!بالفعل
And it feels great to be done with midterms!
،انتهينا من الامتحانات النصفية اليوم أيضاً !فمزاجنا منتعش
Are you alright, Conan-kun?
أأنت بخير يا كونان-كن؟
I wonder if you caught a cold...
أأصابك الزكام؟
You don't seem to have a fever...
لا يبدو أنّك تعاني من حُمى
It's early, but maybe we should go home.
لا يزال الوقت باكراً، لكن ربما علينا الرجوع للمنزل
Oh no!
!كلا
What's wrong?!
ما الخطب؟
I forgot to go to the bank!
!نسيتُ الذهاب للمصرف
The bank?
المصرف؟
Yeah, Dad asked me to cash a check a client wrote him!
أجل، طلب منّي أبي صرف !شيك استلمه من عميل
Wasn't there a bank around here?
أيوجد مصرف بالقرب؟
Toto Bank is just around... that corner.
...يوجد مصرف توتو
Toto Bank- North Beika Park Branch Office
مصرف توتو فرع حديقة شمال بيكا
We just made it, Ran-neechan!
وصلنا قبل فوات الأوان يا ران-نيتشان
Yeah!
نعم
This shouldn't take too long, Conan-kun.
لن يستغرق هذا طويلاً، لننتظر يا كونان-كن
Tsuji Saburo - College Student
تسوجي سابورو طالب جامعيّ
Nagai Takashi (60) Bank Manager
ناغاي تاكاشي موظّف في المصرف
Thank you.
شكراً جزيلاً
Looks like the cold's really going around.
يبدو أنّ الزكام مُنتشر
Hi!
!مرحباً
Ebisawa Kazuo (45) Branch Manager
(45)   إيبيساوا كازو مدير فرع حديقة شمال بيكا لمصرف توتو
Sonoko-ojousama! What brings you here today?
آنسة سونوكو! ما الذي جلبك هنا اليوم؟
I'm just here with a friend...
أرافق صديقتي فحسب
Is that so?
هكذا إذاً
Please give your father my regards.
أوصلي تحيّتي لأبيك رجاءً
Hey, Sonoko. Who was that?
من ذاك الشخص يا سونوكو؟
The branch manager here.
مدير الفرع هنا
The daughter of the Suzuki family shows herself!
!ابنة عائلة مجموعة سوزوكي تظهر نفسها
Conan-kun...
...كونان-كن
Totally sounds like a cold.
يبدو زكاماً حقّاً
You all right, little boy?
أأنت بخير يا صبيّ؟
Taniguchi Noboru Toto Bank Clerk
تانيغوتشي نوبورو أمين صندوق في مصرف توتو
That's a nasty cough. Have some cough drops.
يبدو سعالك شديداً، معي دواء للحلق
You can keep them.
يمكنك أخذه
Thanks!
شكراً
Thank you!
نعتذر على الإزعاج
Not at all.
البتّة
Taniguchi-san! Could you come here?
تانيغوتشي-سان، هلّا أتيت قليلاً؟
Sure!
!نعم
If you'll excuse me.
اعذروني إذاً
It's this...
...إنّه هذا
Lemme see.
دعيني أرى
Maejima Tetsuya (28) Toto Bank Clerk
(مايجيما تيتسويا (28 أمين صندوق في مصرف توتو
Branch Manager. I'm going to make my rounds now.
حضرة المدير، سأذهب لإجراء الجولات الآن
Right. Go get 'em!
حسناً، بالتوفيق
Everyone, stand up with your hands up!
!ارفعوا أيديكم جميعاً وقفوا أماكنكم
Okay! Do anything funny and you're dead!
!إذا أقدمتم على أيّ شيء ستفقدون حياتكم
Move!
!ابتعدي
You deaf or something?!
لا تستطيعين السماع؟
This goin' to one of your clients?!
ستأخذون هذا لأحد عملائكم الأثرياء؟
The world's so unfair!
يا لإجحاف هذا العالم
You, there!
!أنت هناك
Yeah, you! Fill this up!
!أجل، أنت! ضع المال في هذه
The rest, out from behind the counter!
!ليبتعد البقيّة عن الطاولة
Alright! Everyone stay where you are!
!حسناً، ابقوا ساكنين جميعاً
Now fill the bag!
!هيّا، ضع المال في الحقيبة
Ran! What do we do?!
ران، ماذا نفعل؟
We'll be fine if we just stand here.
لا تقلقي، لن يقوم بشيءٍ إذا بقينا أماكننا
Oh no!
!كلا
What the--
!ماذا؟ أنت
Be quiet! Quiet, I say!
!اهدئي! اصمتي
Shut up!
!أخبرتكم أن تصمتوا
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Maejima-san's bullet wound was serious, but not life-threatening.
أُصيب مايجيما-سان في جانب صدره، كان جرحاً بليغاً لكن لا يهدد لحياته لحسن الحظ
So, when Maejima-san went to hit the robber with the wooden sword,
إذاً، عندما همّ مايجيما-سان بضرب الجاني ...بسيف خشبيّ
this cell phone in his pocket went off?
رنّ هذا الهاتف الخلويّ الذي كان في جيب مايجيما-سان؟
That's right. Then the robber turned around, saw him, and fired!
نعم، استدار اللصّ للصوت بعدها ورأى مايجيما-كن وأطلق عليه
And immediately after, you jumped on the robber, Taniguchi-san?
وبعدها، اندفعتَ نحو اللصّ يا تانيغوتشي-سان، صحيح؟
I saw Maejima get shot and then the women started screaming,
رأيتُ تعرّض مايجيما للإطلاق ثمّ بدأت الفتيات بالصراخ
so I panicked.
ففزعت
The robber did too, so he pointed the gun at the women...
...فزع اللصّ بدوره، فوجّه المسدّس نحوهن
The moment things looked bad, I just--
...وعندما شعرتُ بخطورة الوضع، تحرّك جسدي
My only focus was on pointing the gun elsewhere...
كان همّي الوحيد توجيه المسدّس لمكانٍ آخر
Then that happened...
وبعدها حصل ما حصل
Inspector Megure.
مفتّش ميغوري
We're done examining, so you can come back now.
انتهينا من التحليل فيمكنك الدخول الآن
Please wait here a moment.
انتظروا هنا قليلاً من فضلكم
The gun was a modified model gun.
كان المسدّس نموذج لعبة معدّل
And this corner wasn't recorded by the security camera.
أيضاً، لم تظهر هذه الزاوية في تسجيل كاميرات المراقبة
The robber had a cell phone, too...
كان مع اللصّ هاتف خلويّ إذاً
Inspector.
حضرة المفتّش
Saeki Tohru. Born in 1970.
سايكي تورو، وُلِد في 1970
Understood.
فهمت
Does anyone here recognize the robber?
هل يتعرّف أحدكم على وجه الجاني؟
Whoops.
عذراً
Oh, it wasn't me.
لم يكن هاتفي
It's Maejima-san's cell phone.
إنّه هاتف مايجيما-سان الخلويّ
Huh?
ماذا؟
Hello, this is Police Inspector Megure. May I ask who's calling?
،مرحباً، أنا المفتّش ميغوري من مركز الشرطة من معي؟
Koike-san?
كويكي-سان؟
Maejima-san's client.
أحد عملاء مايجيما-سان
Actually, Maejima-san was injured during an incident.
وقعت حادثة وأُصيب فيها مايجيما-سان في الواقع
Pardon my asking, but did you call this phone at around 3:05?
اعذرني على السؤال، لكن هل اتّصلتَ بهذا الهاتف عند قرابة الثالثة وخمس دقائق؟
You didn't?
لم تفعل؟
I see.
فهمت
Hey! Let me listen, too!
!دعني أسمع أيضاً
You recorded during the robbery, right?
كنتَ تسجّل أثناء السطو، صحيح؟
Not so loud! I'm gonna sell this to the media later for a lot!
لا ترفع صوتك! سأبيع هذا للإعلام !بمبلغ باهظ لاحقاً
In that case...
...في تلك الحالة
Fine.
ليس بيدي حيلة
Don't move! Stay right where you are!
!لا تتحرّكوا! ابقوا ساكنين أماكنكم
I thought so!
!كما ظننت
That's enough!
!يكفي
We have some idea about the situation now.
كوّنا فكرة عن وضع الجريمة الآن
Detective!
حضرة الضابط
Will Taniguchi be blamed for what he did?
هل سيُدان تانيغوتشي بما فعله؟
Certainly not!
كلا
Had he not jumped at the robber, you folks might've been shot!
،لو لم يندفع نحو اللصّ لربما أطلق عليكم
He acted courageously and risked his own life!
أبدى شجاعةً وخاطر بحياته
If anything, he should be rewarded!
من الحريّ أن يُكافأ، لكن لن يُدان البتّة
Is that so?! That's great news, Taniguchi!
!حقّاً؟! هذا رائع يا تانيغوتشي
We owe you a reward, as well!
!علينا مُكافأتك بدورنا
No...
...لا
Maejima-san was unlucky, though.
لكن لم يحالف الحظّ مايجيما-سان
We still don't know who called him.
لا نزال نجهل من اتّصل به
If his phone hadn't rung just then, he might never have been shot...
،لكن لو لم يرنّ هاتفه مصادفةً آنذاك لتفادى التعرّض للإطلاق
No! Everyone's got it all wrong!
!كلا، الجميع يسيئون الفهم
Here it is!
!ها هو
This isn't a toy, little boy. It's important.
لا يصحّ هذا يا ولد! إنّه غرضٌ مهم فلا يمكنك العبث به
Taniguchi-san. I'll be filing the report,
تانيغوتشي-سان، علينا كتابة التقرير
so could you accompany me to the station?
لذا هلّا رافقتنا للمركز لتقديم إفادتك؟
All right.
حسناً
I need to use the restroom first.
عليّ الذهاب للحمّام قبلها
Sure thing.
تفضّل
What is it, little boy?
ما-ما الخطب يا فتى؟
Need the restroom?
تحتاج الذهاب للحمّام؟
Yeah...
...نعم
Oh...
...هكذا إذاً
Why did Taniguchi-san get nervous and hide his phone?
لمَ انتاب تانيغوتشي-سان الهلع وأخفى هاتفه؟
Was he trying to call somewhere? Or--
...أكان يحاول الاتّصال بمكانٍ ما؟ أم
Could there be another side to this case?!
!لعلّ هناك جانباً خلفياً لهذه القضيّة
To think you kids were involved, too...
لم يخطر لي أن تكونا عالقتين في القضيّة
It's a miracle you weren't hurt!
حمداً لله أنّكما لم تُصابا بأذى
A card-based security lock.
قفل أمان يُفتح ببطاقة
Taniguchi-san's jacket!
!معطف تانيغوتشي-سان
Come to think of it...
...صحيح، آنذاك
what was the robber looking for?
ما الذي كان يبحث عنه الجاني؟
Cigarettes? A lighter? I doubt it...
...سجائر؟ قدّاحة؟ لا أظنّ
Then what, exactly?
ماذا إذاً؟
Empty...
...لا شيء
Wait! Before that, he--
...لحظة! رمى قبل ذلك
It was right around here...
كانت في هذه الأرجاء
This is...
...هذه
I've figured it out!
!فهمت
So, this case does have a more sinister side!
كان لهذه القضيّة جانب !خلفيّ مُظلم
The old man's not here today, so I'll have to rely on Sonoko again!
العمّ ليس موجوداً اليوم، لذا ليس بيدي !حيلة، سأعتمد على سونوكو مُجدداً
Sorry to keep you waiting.
آسفٌ على الإطالة
I'm sorry to burden you after all that's happened...
نعتذر على مضايقتك بعدما مررت به
Say, Ran!
...ران، اسمعي
What is it, Sonoko? Sonoko?
ماذا يا سونوكو؟ سونوكو؟
Not again...
...مُجدداً
Sonoko!
!سونوكو؟
Inspector, I've figured it out.
حضرة المفتّش، لقد عرفت
Figured what out, Sonoko-kun?
عرفتِ ماذا يا سونوكو-كن؟
There's a sinister side to this thingy, err, dealy!
...لهذه القضيّة جانب خلفيّ
"Thingy, err, dealy"?
خلفي... متغطٍّ؟
I mean incident!
!أقصد جانب خفيّ
Boy, it's hard to talk like a girl!
!من الصعب الكلام كفتاة
To begin with, what rang when Maejima-san went to use the sword
بدايةً، الرنين الذي صدر عندما همّ مايجيما-سان بمهاجمة الجاني بالسيف الخشبيّ
was not his phone, but the robber's!
!لم يكن من هاتفه، بل هاتف الجاني
Impossible! Everyone's confirmed that it was his phone that rang!
مستحيل! الجميع متأكدون أنّ الرنين !صدر من هاتف مايجيما-سان وقتها
But when his cell phone rang earlier,
،لكن عندما رنّ هاتفه قبل قليل
both you and Taniguchi-san mistakenly grabbed your own phones!
مددتَ وتانيغوتشي-سان يديكما بالخطأ لهاتفيكما
Similarly, everyone thought it was Maejima-san's phone that rang!
بنفس الشكل، اعتقد الجميع آنذاك أنّ هاتف مايجيما-سان كان من أصدر الرنين
That is possible, but how are you sure it was the robber's phone instead?
ذلك مُحتمل بالفعل، لكن ما الذي يجعلك مقتنعة أنّه كان هاتف اللصّ بالفعل؟
The ringtone.
نغمة الرنين
The ringtone?
نغمة الرنين؟
Compare the ringtones of the two phones and you'll see.
قارن نغمتَي هاتف مايجيما-سان واللصّ وسترى بنفسك
Also, that college guy has the ringtone from the robbery on tape!
أيضاً، قام الطالب الجامعيّ بتسجيل النغمة التي صدرت وقت الجريمة
Is this true? Do you have this?!
!أهذا صحيح؟! هل سجّلتها؟
No!
!لا
Quit yer lyin'!
!لا تكذب يا هذا
I did it again!
...فعلتُها مجدداً
I mean, don't bother lying! I know you do!
،لا، أقصد أنّ الكذب لن ينفعك !فأنا متأكدة
Well?! Help us out if you have it!
!إذاً؟ تعاون معنا إذا التسجيل معك
Okay, okay... but give it back later!
!حسناً، لكن فلتعيدوه لاحقاً رجاءً
Inspector! I got a tape player!
!حضرة المفتّش، أحضرت مشغّل كاسيت
Maejima
مايجيما
Bank Robber
اللصّ
Alright, let's begin.
سأبدأ إذاً
Please.
فلتفعل
First, Maejima-san's cell phone.
هاتف مايجيما-سان أولاً
Next, the robber's cell phone.
ثمّ، هاتف اللصّ تالياً
It's the same sound, but a different pattern...
الصوت نفسه، لكنّ نمطه مختلف
And here's the one during the incident...
...وهذا الرنين وقت الحادثة
Shut up! Shut up!
!اصمتي! اصمتي
A little before that!
قبل ذلك بقليل
Right!
!حسناً
Go back again!
!ارجع مجدداً
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
That's definitely the ringtone from the robber's cell phone.
هذا نمط نغمة رنين هاتف اللصّ بالفعل
Sonoko-kun. Just as you said,
سونوكو-كن، كما قلتِ
it seems it was the robber's phone that rang.
يبدو أنّ هاتف اللصّ كان ما أصدر الرنين وقتها
Did someone just happen to call his phone then, or--
...هل اتّصل أحدهم بهاتفه مصادفةً؟ أم
It was likely his accomplice who called.
كان شريكه من اتّصل غالباً
Accomplice?!
!شريكه؟
That accomplice saw Maejima-san about to hit him with the sword,
رأى ذاك الشريك استعداد مايجيما-سان لضرب اللصّ بالسيف الخشبيّ
and quickly called the robber's phone using his own...
فاتّصل بهاتف اللصّ سريعاً !باستعمال هاتفه الخاص
to warn him of the danger!
لتنبيهه على الخطر
What?! Then that means his accomplice is still in here!
،مـ-ماذا؟! في تلك الحالة !لا يزال الشريك موجوداً هنا
Yes. And that would be you, Taniguchi-san!
نعم، وذلك الشريك هو !أنت يا تانيغوتشي-سان
You can't be serious. Don't joke like that.
ما الذي تقولينه؟ توقّفي عن المزاح رجاءً
Taniguchi-san.
تانيغوتشي-سان
First, you used your cell phone to signal the robber outside
قمتَ أوّلاً بالاتّصال باللصّ الذي كان ينتظر قرب المصرف خارجاً
to bust inside at just the right time.
لإخباره باللحظة المناسبة للاقتحام
Because the staff door opens from the inside when someone leaves,
ذلك لأنّ الباب المخصّص للموظفين يُفتح من الداخل عندما يغادر أحدهم
but you need a card to get in from the outside!
!لكنّك تحتاج بطاقة للدخول من الخارج
Branch Manager. I'm going to make my rounds now.
حضرة المدير، سأذهب لإجراء الجولات الآن
Right, that's it.
أجل، هكذا
Hold on a sec while I get the list.
تمهلي قليلاً، سأذهب لجلب اللائحة
Alright.
حسناً
Everyone stand up with your hands up!
!ارفعوا أيديكم جميعاً وقفوا أماكنكم
Then, as planned, you filled the bag with cash as he ordered,
بعدها، ملأت الحقيبة بالنقود تحت أمر اللصّ وفقما خططتما
and were the only one left behind the counter.
وكنتَ الوحيد خلف طاولة الموظّفين
Looking back, he barely seemed concerned about you!
تذكرتُ الآن، لم يبدِ أي اهتمام تجاهك
Your original plan had him leaving without hurting anyone
كانت خطّتك تتضمّن ألّا يؤذي اللصّ أحداً
and making off with the money-filled bag!
وأن يهرب بعد استلامه الحقيبة المليئة بالمال منك
Then, you'd meet up with him later to split the money!
كنتما ستلتقيان لاحقاً لاقتسام النقود
But something unexpected happened!
!لكن وقع أمرٌ خارج الحسبان
Maejima-san regained consciousness!
!استرجع مايجيما-سان وعيه
You wanted to warn him somehow.
أردتَ تنبيهه بشكلٍ ما
You probably wanted to shout, "Behind you!"
،أردتَ أن تصرخ "وراءك!" في الواقع
but that would've exposed you.
لكن كان ذلك ليكشف أمرك
Thinking quickly...
،عندها فكّرتَ سريعاً
...you pressed your redial button.
وضغطت زرّ إعادة الاتّصال على الهاتف
The robber's phone rang, but Maejima-san thought it was his own
رنّ هاتف اللصّ، لكن ظنّ مايجيما-سان أنّه كان هاتفه
and was shot when he froze!
وتعرّض للإطلاق عندما توقّف مكانه
The biggest mistake, in your eyes, was when he shot him.
أكبر خلل في الحسابات كان برأيك عندما أطلق على مايجيما-سان
The robber lost his cool and looked ready to shoot other people.
فقد اللصّ تماسكه فجأةً، وبدا أنّه قد يطلق على البقيّة
Realizing that the plan was out of control, you jumped at him...
أدركتَ أنّ الاستمرار بالخطّة قد ...يكون خطيراً، فقفزت عليه
...and shut him up by pretending to shoot him during the struggle!
وأسكتّه بالتظاهر بمحاولتك إبعاد المسدّس بينما أطلقت عليه
This is nonsense! She's just making this up!
هذا هراء، إنّها ادّعاءات لا أساس لها فحسب
Could I see your cell phone?
هلّا أريتنا هاتفك الخلويّ؟
If she's right, the redial button should call the robber's phone.
إذا كانت محقّة، فسيطلب زرّ إعادة الاتّصال رقم هاتف اللصّ
Certainly.
لا بأس
I thought so!
!كما ظننت
You erased your redial memory when you went to the restroom!
محوتَ ذاكرة إعادة الاتّصال !عندما ذهبت للحمّام قبل قليل
Inspector. There's definitive proof that they were accomplices.
حضرة المفتّش، يوجد دليل دامغ يثبت كونهما شريكين
Are you serious, Sonoko-kun?!
!حقّاً يا سونوكو-كن؟
Conan-kun.
كونان-كن
Right!
!حاضر
Inspector. Put your hands out.
حضرة المفتّش، افتح يديك
Like this?
هكذا؟
Here you go!
!هاك
What is this?
ما هذه؟
Cough drops! I got them from Taniguchi-san before the robbery!
حبوب سعال، أعطاني إيّاها تانيغوتشي-سان قبل وقوع السرقة
Sonoko-neechan! I handed them over!
!سونوكو-نيتشان! أنا من أعطيته إيّاها
Inspector. In your right hand is paper the robber threw away.
حضرة المفتّش، الورقة في يدك اليمنى هي التي ألقاها اللصّ
Right afterwards, he fumbled around in Taniguchi-san's jacket pockets!
بعد فعله ذلك، كان ينبش في جيوب معطف تانيغوتشي-سان
He was looking for cough drops.
كان يبحث عن دواء السعال
He and Taniguchi-san probably met somewhere this afternoon
التقى مع تانيغوتشي-سان ظهيرة اليوم في مكانٍ ما غالباً
for a final meeting.
لأجل اجتماعٍ أخير
Both had colds and sore throats,
كان الاثنان يعانيان من الزكام وحنجرة ملتهبة
so one of them split a pack of cough drops and gave half to the other.
فقسم أحدهما دواء السعال الذي معه لنصفين وأعطاه للآخر
Afterwards, the robber's throat hurt again after shouting
بعدها، أصبحت حنجرة اللصّ تؤلمه مجدداً عند وصوله إلى هنا
so, he went to get a cough drop from his pocket, but they were all gone
،أدخل يده في جيبه لإخراج الحبوب لكن كانت قد نفدت
and only the wrapper remained.
ولم يبق إلّا الغلاف
Then, he remembered Taniguchi-san had some in his jacket pocket
عندها، تذكّر اللصّ أنّ تانيغوتشي-سان يملك نصفاً في جيب معطفه
and went to get them...
وحاول أخذه
...unaware he had given them away to Conan-kun.
في جهله من إعطاء تانيغوتشي-سان إيّاها لكونان
As proof, the tears on the wrappers should fit perfectly!
ودليلاً على ذلك، يُفترض أن يتّصل !نصفا الغلاف تماماً
You're right!
!إنّها الحقيقة
Also, fingerprints from Taniguchi-san or the robber should be on both!
أيضاً، بصمات تانيغوتشي-سان أو القاتل ستكون على النصفين معاً
Have them checked at once.
اطلب فحصهما فوراً
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
Taniguchi-san. Do you have anything to say?
تانيغوتشي-سان، هل لديك ما تقوله؟
Saeki gave me the cough drops.
كان سايكي من أعطاني حبوب السعال
I met him through a loan shark.
التقيتُه عبر مُرابي قروض
We came up with this robbery to repay the loan and for play money.
وخطّطنا لعملية السطو هذه لردّ الديون واللهو بالمال الزائد
Had I known this would happen,
،لو كنتُ أعرف حصول هذا
I wouldn't have given you the cough drops.
لما أعطيتُك حبوب السعال
You're incredible, Sonoko! You solved another case!
!مُذهل يا سونوكو! حللتِ قضيّة أخرى
I don't remember much, but I felt this sharp pinprick--
لا أتذكّر الكثير، لكنّي شعرت ...بوخز إبرة وراء عنقي
Pinprick?
وخز؟
Yikes!
!تبّاً
But Shinichi-kun has nothing on me!
لكن، لم يعد شينتشي-كن يحتلّ الساحة
It's all about the cute and charming high school detective Suzuki Sonoko!
الأضواء الآن ستُسلّط على متحريّة المدرسة الثانوية !الظريفة والساحرة، سوزوكي سونوكو
Darn it! I knew I shouldn't have used her!
!تبّاً! كان عليّ ألّا أستعملها حقّاً
Such regrets...
...يا للندم
She's the killer!
لكن لا دليل لديّ
But I have no proof!
جريمة قتل الفنّان المتجوّل
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
House cleaning.
تنظيف منزليّ
She's the culprit.
!هي المجرمة
I know that.
نعرف ذلك